[theme music playing]
Once I return to Poblacion Ardiente,
I will clean up the trash that
gathered there while I was away.
[Emilia] I don't understand!
Why can't he just die?!
He will regret coming back here
to Poblacion Ardiente.
Mayor, some of our men saw Miss Aguas
leave right after Mr. Raul.
-[screams]
-[glass shatters]
-[Belen] Raul, Jasmin got away!
-Where is Jasmin?!
-[Belen] Look for her!
-[tires screech]
Mom? Mom, it's me. It's me, Lily.
I'm sure it was her.
But she ran from me.
I couldn't catch up to her.
But I'm sure that was my mom.
I'm confused if she's referring
to Prianka Aguas or Camia Cruz.
I have a hunch that Ivy
and Lily are the same person.
-[Raul] I have to hide Camia.
-Camia? Who is Camia?
[Emilia] I don't like women
flirting with my husband.
I don't intend on tainting my reputation
by sleeping with your useless husband.
Project your insecurity
elsewhere, but not on me.
[Belen] He told me her name was Jasmin.
Raul left with Camia last night
and went somewhere far away.
-[Ivy] Raul Torillo?
-He has Camia.
[Emilia] I missed you. Welcome back!
[Julio] You can't fool me
with your crocodile tears,
hugs, and kisses.
I know what you've been doing.
This is not happening, right?
This can't be happening!
He cannot take everything away from me!
He cannot do this to me!
-Auntie, I cannot win!
-Calm down, Emilia.
You can't allow Julio to smell your fear!
That was the downfall of your mother.
And I'll be damned
if I let that happen to you!
He may be Julio Ardiente,
but he's only just a man!
Do you understand me?!
[Carlotta] You have to
wash this again, okay?
-[maid] Okay.
-All right. Make sure of that.
[breathes heavily]
-[Ivy screams]
-Dear!
That monster!
[panting] That animal, Raul,
has my mother.
Ivy, you can save your mother.
You will save your mother.
I know I will.
I'll save my mother from that
bastard, Nanny Carlotta.
[quietly] Yes, you will.
-Where's Jepoy?!
-Uh…
-[Carlotta] Dear…
-Ivy.
Jepoy, we were right. Our hunch was right!
That animal, Raul, has my mother, Jepoy!
Go back to the Ardientes!
We'll communicate through
our cell phones for now.
When Raul goes back to the
Ardientes, update me right away.
We need to keep a closer eye on Raul.
He's the key to saving my mother.
So, I can see her again.
Of all people!
That bastard, Raul! He has my mother.
You'll be with your mother again, Ivy.
-I'm sure of that.
-Yes, you will.
Yes, I'll be with her again.
I'll save her from that bastard!
[tense music playing]
Jasmin?
Jasmin. Here's your food.
I cooked it myself, so you'd feel better.
Jasmin?
I know you're upset with me
because of what I did,
but I only did it to protect you.
And…
[Raul clicks tongue]
Jasmin, I'm sorry.
I love you very much.
I'll never… I'll never…
I'll never hurt you again. Believe me.
Eat now, Jasmin. We'll be okay here.
[sobs, screams]
-Jasmin. Jasmin, wait!
-[screaming, sobbing]
-Jasmin.
-[Jasmin panting]
[sighs]
[panting]
That's enough.
Jasmin, that's enough.
I'm here for you.
I won't leave you. Calm down.
Nobody will get in between us.
-[Camia] Sir, excuse me.
-[Raul] Wait…
[Camia] Sir, please don't… Don't touch me!
[sobs, screams]
-[screaming continues]
-Jasmin!
-[Jasmin screaming]
-Jasmin.
[Jasmin screaming, sobbing]
-Calm down. Calm down.
-[sobbing continues]
[Raul shushes]
[sobbing continues]
-[shushes] Calm down.
-[Jasmin sobbing]
-[stutters] I won't--
-[sobbing continues]
-[Raul shushes]
[Raul sniffles]
[dramatic tense music playing]
[birds chirping]
Hey, Nanny, Uncle!
-[giggling]
-I didn't see you there.
How do I look?
Great!
That's the Diego we know.
He never gives up.
Well, I realized that it
doesn't matter if Ivy is Lily.
For now, I won't worry about
all the secrets she's keeping.
[exhales sharply] What's
important is how I feel for her.
That's what will set us free.
No matter how many times
she turns me down--
-You'll never say die!
-[laughter]
[exhales] I love her.
Excuse me. [knocking]
Oh! Hi, Mayor! Please come in.
Um… You probably heard
that Grandpa is back.
He sent me to fetch you.
What if I don't go?
What if I don't let you? Come on.
Grandpa sent your beloved
brother here to fetch you
and make sure you'll come.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Emilia.
Have a seat, Papa.
[laughs]
[Julio grunts]
[Julio groans]
Well?
Why are you just standing there?
Sit down.
You're like a mushroom, Clarita.
You popped up out of nowhere.
You even chose to show up
just when I wasn't here.
Anyway… why isn't Miss Aguas here?
Why isn't she here to welcome me?
She's busy, Papa.
Oh! Is she, Emilia?
With what? Playing you for a sap?
[Julio laughs] Oh, Emilia!
You never did learn to use your brain.
-Julio, that's enough.
-No one tells me what to do!
And I certainly won't take it from you.
Have you forgotten that you're
just a guest here in my home?!
And you, Emilia.
You allowed Ivy to toy around with you
in the palm of her hand.
Well, that stops now!
From now on,
I'll be the one to talk to Ivy.
I'll make her pay for
everything she owes me.
Arnaldo.
Pick Miss Aguas up tomorrow, and
tell her I want to talk to her.
Yes, Grandpa.
It's time to find out
if that woman is with us or against us.
You know very well what happens
to our family's enemies, right?
[suspenseful sting]
[tense music playing]
Now where is that husband
of yours, Emilia?
Why isn't he here?
Isn't he glad that I'm back?
Well… Maybe it's better
he isn't here because…
who knows what could happen
to him now that I'm back.
What are you planning to do to Dad?
He didn't do anything to you!
[laughs]
Hasn't your mother told you yet?
Papa, please not now.
Why, Emilia?
What are you afraid
your sons will find out?
That your no-good husband
is a worthless piece of--
Grandpa… Grandpa… Think about your heart.
[tense music playing]
I didn't come here to listen
to you insult my father!
I'm leaving.
Before you go, Diego.
I want you to remember…
Even if you no longer live in this house,
you still have duties to fulfill.
Because in the eyes of the public,
this family is complete, happy,
and loves one another.
And it will stay that way!
And now that I'm back, we will
repair this family's image.
I'm done pretending for you, Grandpa.
And I am willing to protect all
the important people…
in my life from this family!
[tense music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
Well then, let's eat.
[cutlery clinking]
[tense music playing]
Where could Raul have taken my mother?
Ivy, aside from his Aunt Belen,
maybe Raul has other relatives.
[Ivy exhales]
[phone ringing]
-Ivy.
-Jepoy, any news on Raul?
He didn't show up here.
And it looks like he's never going to.
-What makes you say that?
-Julio's back, Ivy.
Señor Julio has returned
to Poblacion Ardiente.
We have to be more careful.
I'll speed up my search
for my mother, Jepoy.
And you… You are on the Ardientes' turf.
Be careful.
-Ivy, I'll help you.
-Thank you.
Let's keep in touch.
Goodbye.
Bye.
[tense music playing]
I'll give Papa his medication.
Okay, ma'am.
-Papa.
-[scoffs] Emilia.
You wouldn't try to poison
me again, would you?
Just like what you did
when we were in America.
[clicks tongue] It's a good
thing my nurse was sharp
and noticed the poison you tried
to pass off as my medication.
What? Oh, come on! Cat got your tongue?
Aren't you going to deny it?
You must be so proud or callous…
to try and kill your own father.
What would Arnaldo say
if he found out about that?
Or if he finds out
that his father strangled me,
which led me to have a heart attack,
almost killing me in the process.
What do you think?
Don't you dare, Julio.
If I let you hurt my sister back then…
not now. Not with Emilia!
[laughs]
Looks like my brilliant
daughter found herself an ally.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Remember, anyone who
opposes me will be punished.
And you, Emilia…
I'll make you suffer.
You'll see just how cruel
your father can be.
[tense music playing]
[whispers] Emilia.
[engine stops]
[soft music playing]
[doorbell rings]
-[doorbell rings]
-It's Diego.
-[Ivy sighs]
-[quietly] I'll get it.
[door opens]
-Diego.
-Miss Carlotta.
-[Carlotta] Yes, Diego?
-[Diego] Good evening.
[Carlotta] Good evening.
Can I talk to Ivy?
Oh, no. She's asleep.
She went to bed early.
Miss Carlotta, please.
I have something important to tell her.
[Carlotta] You can leave her a message.
I'll just relay it to her, Diego.
[sighs]
Grandpa wants to meet with her tomorrow.
Please tell her to be careful
and not to go with them.
All right. I'll tell her. Thank you.
And one more thing…
Um…
Please give these to her.
[Carlotta] Of course.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Bye.
-Thanks again.
-All right. Goodnight.
[Carlotta] Goodnight.
[door closes]
[soft music playing]
He asked me to give you this.
You know what to do with that, Nanny.
Ivy.
How long are you going to avoid Diego?
I don't have time to think
about Diego right now, Nanny.
What's more important to me…
is I find my mother.
And I also need to make sure
all my loved ones are safe…
from the Ardientes. That's my priority.
[soft guitar music playing]
[Diego] I can't explain it.
Whenever we're together,
I feel like I'm with Lily again.
Did you ever have a
best friend when you were a kid?
I was a loner.
I was always cooped up in my room.
All I did was read.
Really? I love to read too.
Just like Lily.
Do you know The Count of Monte Cristo?
[Ivy] "Moral wounds have this peculiarity.
They may be hidden, but they never close."
[Diego] "Always painful, always
ready to bleed when touched,
they remain fresh and open in the heart."
[young Diego] Why do you
always have that with you?
The Count of Monte Cristo.
I love it when my father reads this to me.
Ivy, what happened?
My mom…
Ivy, Prianka's been dead for years.
I'm confused if she's referring
to Prianka Aguas or Camia Cruz.
I have a hunch that Ivy
and Lily are the same person.
Ivy, I didn't know you had a sister.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why are you keeping secrets?
I didn't tell you about her
because it's still a very
sensitive topic for me.
I guess you won't understand
because you've never lost
a loved one before.
I know the feeling. I've lost someone too.
Diego, Lily just disappeared,
she didn't die.
They're different things.
[Loring] Maybe you're
falling in love with Miss Ivy
because you think that she's Lily.
What if that's not true?
Would you still be in love with Miss Ivy?
[soft guitar music playing]
[soft instrumental music playing]
[Ivy] I know I make a lot
of risky decisions.
Decisions that make you
worry. But you're still here.
To be honest, you do so much for me.
Sometimes, you risk your life
because you're one of Arnaldo's men,
but you still continue to help me.
You're always there for me.
You're a good friend, Jepoy.
[Jepoy] You're not mad he kissed
you? Ivy, he disrespected you!
I hit him right after
if that's what you want to hear.
That's not enough!
I could beat him to a pulp.
Break a few bones if you want!
Wait, why are you acting like this?
Ivy, I just want to protect
you from the Ardientes.
Especially from those brothers!
[tense music playing]
[Julio] She's smart. She's beautiful.
Financially independent.
Looks like my perception
of women is starting to change.
[Emilia] I know that you've been
lusting after Ivy the minute
that you laid your eyes on her.
[Arnaldo] No target has ever
escaped my trap.
No matter what happens,
you will be mine, Ivy.
[tense music playing]
From now on, I'll be the one
to talk to Ivy.
It's time to find out if that
woman is with us or against us.
[tense music playing]
[Prianka] So, what do you want, Lily?
I want justice for my mom and dad!
Then, we have a deal.
[Prianka] Remember everything
I taught you.
Do what you must do.
Make them pay!
Miss Prianka.
[tense music playing]
I wouldn't be where I am today
if not for you, Miss Prianka.
Fate's a funny thing.
But in the end, it was still your guidance
that led me to find my mother.
I promise I won't fail.
-[Emilia sobbing]
-This can't be, Emilia.
[sobbing] Auntie, this can't happen!
This can't happen!
I don't know what Papa might do to me,
you, and worst of all, Raul!
Look at me, Emilia.
I'll take care of Julio for you.
I am willing to go
to such lengths for you.
After what he did to my sister,
I can never forgive him!
Auntie, I need you now.
I need someone on my side.
I need you more now, Auntie.
We can do this, Emilia.
Do you hear me?
[unsettling music playing]
[music intensifies]
Let's go, Madrigal.
-Where to, Mayor?
-Miss Aguas.
Does she know we're dropping by?
She might not be there.
I want to surprise her.
Wouldn't that be nice?
You helped her surprise me yourself.
You're right about that, Mayor.
Good.
I'm glad you know your job, Madrigal.
[tense music playing]
I want you to help me
get what I want from Miss Aguas.
-Let's go.
-Yes, Mayor.
[tense music playing]
[car horn honks]
-Hey, Diego!
-[engine stops]
Uncle! What are you doing here?
[chuckles] I was hitching
a ride with Fernan,
but his car broke down.
So, I decided to just walk.
I could use the exercise.
I'm on my way to your place.
Loring got there first.
Are you going somewhere?
That can wait. Let me give you a ride.
No, don't let me keep you.
I think you're going somewhere important.
Of course, I won't let you get tired.
-Come on. Get in.
-Well, if you insist.
[Diego] What happened to the car?
-I'm not sure.
-[engine starts]
It suddenly stopped.
-That's bad.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
You should tell Mr. Fernan
to go buy a new one.
[Pandoy chuckling] I will.
See, this is better than exercise!
I'll just drive you,
so you won't get tired.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Ivy. You have a visitor.
Mr. Mayor.
-Good morning, Miss Aguas.
-Good morning.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Before anything else, I don't get it.
Why are you becoming
more beautiful every day?
[Ivy chuckles] Thank you.
I'm sure the Congressman
will be happy to see you.
He'll be happy to see me?
I don't remember making
an appointment with him.
You have one now.
I'm sure you don't want to upset him.
So, you'll come, right?
[tense music playing]
Of course! Why would I
turn down Congressman Julio?
So, should I meet him at his house?
You'll find out. Shall we?
Okay. I have to go, Nanny.
All right, Ivy.
[tense music playing]
[soft ominous music playing]
[music intensifies]
I won't let anything happen to you.
I will protect you from my family.
[clicks tongue] Do you think that…
we're doing the right thing
by letting Diego pursue
his feelings for Ivy or Lily,
or whoever that woman is?
Well, Diego's not a kid anymore, Loring.
He's already been through a lot.
Don't you think it's only right
for him to find his happiness?
Not if it will put his life in danger.
[Pandoy clicks tongue, exhales sharply]
It's Diego's decision
to take a risk on love.
All we can do is support him.
If he gets hurt,
then let's stay by his side
until he recovers from the pain.
[sighs deeply]
[Pandoy exhales]
Congressman Julio!
Welcome back! It's nice to see you back.
It's nice to be back, Miss Aguas.
Please, sit down.
Thank you.
-Would you care for some tea?
-No, I'm good. Thank you.
So, where's Emilia?
[chuckles] Emilia doesn't need
to be part of this conversation.
Actually, I'm more interested
in your report
about our supposed projects and plans.
Supposedly.
[chuckles] You want me
to deliver the report?
Congressman, I shouldn't
be the one doing that.
Arnaldo can do it himself.
Actually, he already did.
He already told me everything,
especially about how
you helped the farmers.
-[Ivy] Stop!
-[Arnaldo] Miss Aguas!
-[Pandoy] Butchoy!
-[Ivy] Stop!
-Butchoy, what are you doing?
It's okay. It's okay.
Mr. Mayor, make them stop!
There's an innocent child here!
[Julio] Aside from that,
you transferred the EPZ site,
and you even bought
the land for the farmers.
[Pandoy] Thank you so much.
We are forever indebted to you.
[Fernan] He's right, Miss Ivy.
You've been helping us
ever since the dispersal.
[farmer] That's right.
[clicks tongue] Admirable.
By the way, I also heard
that you had some dealings
with my late friend, Pablo.
Would it be all right if I ask
what you two talked about?
Uh… Does it have something to do…
with the plan to bring me down?
[both laugh]
Congressman… I see you're
still good at cracking jokes.
[sighs] Nothing like that, Congressman.
The truth is I wanted to support
Arnaldo in his decision
to take over your position.
But then, you know how Emilia is.
You've probably heard about what she did.
I heard. Well, you'll
have to excuse Arnaldo.
He didn't have the heart
to push through with it.
He has a lot to learn about
being a go-getter, like me.
You know, Miss Aguas…
You should give me
the money you promised me.
I mean, we should join forces.
Can you imagine what we can achieve?
With your wealth and my influence.
[tense music playing]
You want me to give it so soon?
You just got back, Congressman.
I see Emilia really does take after you.
[chuckles lightly]
The election's still far off.
Now's not the time.
There's a right time for that.
I have to go, Congressman.
Enjoy your breakfast.
Good morning, Miss Aguas.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Grandpa. Where's Ivy?
[Julio] Hmm.
[tense music intensifies]
[music fades]
[Emilia] Hello, Raul? Listen to me.
Don't come to the house just yet.
I'm sure Papa will have you killed.
You better stay at your
parents' place in San Ildefonso.
Don't come here. I'll go to you…
when things have settled down here.
Emilia, that's not the best idea.
Your father can still find me there.
Besides, I've found
another place to stay at.
That's good, then.
Raul, you have to help me bring down Papa.
Otherwise, he'll have both our heads.
Please, Emilia. Stop this.
Don't drag me into those
stupid plans of yours.
[grunts, sighs]
Hmm!
San Ildefonso. The Torillos' old house.
That's where Raul
could be hiding my mother.
[sighs]
Everything will go back to normal.
Even if it's just us. You and me.
I'll take care of you. I won't lose you.
[dramatic tense music playing]
Why? Did you think
we could get it that easy?
That woman will make us work for it.
You know, Arnaldo, I have a suspicion
that Miss Aguas is hiding something.
I want you to follow her.
Find out where she goes.
Yes, Grandpa. Madrigal, let's go.
Where are you going, Ivy?
Who are you looking for?
Diego? Why is he following me?
[tense music playing]
Faster, Madrigal.
We need to know where Ivy's going.
She might meet my good-for-nothing dad
to plan something against Grandpa.
Yes, Mayor.
WE ARE FOLLOWING YOU.
[phone chimes]
You too, Arnaldo?
Why are they following me?
There! Follow her car.
Mayor, we'll take the other road.
There's an intersection at the end.
We can catch her there.
What?
[tense music playing]
Where is she?
-[clicks tongue, sighs]
-Where's Ivy?!
Damn it, Madrigal!
I told you not to lose her!
Mayor, I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
Did you do it intentionally?!
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo breathes heavily]
It's important that I can trust
my staff, Madrigal.
Your loyalty should only
be to me and my family.
Because if not, you might end up dead.
It would be a shame if that happens.
[footsteps fading]
[exhales]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[Camia groans]
-Jasmin. What's wrong?
-[Camia groaning]
-What's wrong?
-[groaning]
Jasmin, what's wrong? Hold on.
Where are you going?
Jasmin, wait! Love, stop.
Where are you going? You can't go outside.
[grunts]
-Come. Sit down. Tell me.
-[groaning]
What's wrong? Tell me.
-Tell me.
Where does it hurt? Your stomach?
Hmm?
[Camia sobbing, grunting]
All right. Listen to me.
This is what we'll do.
I'll go outside to buy medicine,
but I need to lock you up here.
I want you to be safe. I'm sorry, love.
There's food there if you want to eat.
I'll be back soon.
[sobbing, gasping]
[Camia groaning]
[Camia gasping]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music playing]
[car unlocks]
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[wailing]
Anyone who opposes me will be punished.
And you, Emilia, I'll make you suffer.
You'll see just how
cruel your father can be.
[wailing]
[squeals]
[wailing, screaming]
[glass shatters]
[wailing]
Emilia!
[sobbing] Auntie…
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[Emilia sobbing]
Emilia, you aren't alone in
your fight against your father.
I'm here for you.
We will bring him down by whatever means!
Do you understand me?
I promise you that.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobs]
I'm here, Emilia.
[Emilia sobbing]
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
[Emilia sobbing]
The Torillos' residence?
Oh, they're well-known here.
Mr. Torillo is Congressman
Ardiente's best friend…
while his son became
Governor Emilia's husband.
I see. Is their house still far from here?
It is. I'd say around a two-hour ride.
You can find it beyond those fields.
How do I get there?
Go straight ahead, and you'll
eventually see a steep road.
There, you'll find
an old lone house there.
But I'm not sure
if anyone still lives in it.
All right, thank you.
[engine starts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[doorbell ringing]
Hey, Diego.
-Has Ivy come home yet?
-Not yet.
Did she tell you what time
she'll be coming back?
Is there a problem, Diego?
Do you remember
what I told you last night?
Don't worry. I won't leave
until she comes back.
Okay. Come inside. Wait here.
-[mugs clinking]
-Oh, no!
-[mugs break]
-What--
-My goodness!
-I knew it! Good grief!
-Goodness, Loring!
I knew it!
-Loring, snap out of it.
-My gut is telling me
that something bad is going to happen!
Loring. Loring. Loring.
Loring, nothing bad is going to happen!
You dropped that because you got
clumsy from worrying so much.
Can you blame me?
[Carlotta] Diego, have a seat.
I'll get you something to drink, okay?
-Okay, thank you.
-Okay.
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
[dramatic music]
[young Lily] The Count of Monte Cristo.
I love it when my father reads this to me.
Do you know The Count of Monte Cristo?
It's an amazing book.
[tense music playing]
Pa, the people at the office
are very happy that you're back.
What about you, Emilia? Are you happy?
-Of course, Papa. I'm--
-Don't lie to me!
Tonight, all your lies
will come to an end!
[Diego] I'm sure of it. That girl is Lily.
I need to know the truth.
-Mom, are you here?
-[Camia screams]
[dishes shatter]
[grunts] Mom!
[sobs] Mom. Mom! Mom. Mom.
Love, what is it? Is there
something you want to tell me?
[theme music playing]